sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
dareka no kitai ni zutto kotae
are you really happy
homerarerunoga suki nano desuka
when you're always meeting to someone's expectations?
naritai jibun wo surikaetemo
even if you change to who you really wanna be
egao wa itsudemo suteki desuka
will you always have a great smile?
hajimaridake yume mite okiru
dreaming of only the beginning, I wake up
sono saki nara itsuka jibun no ude de
and someday, I'll live on my own.
souda daiji na mono wa itsumo katachi no nai mono dake
yes, precious things are never in shape
te ni iretemo nakushitemo kizukanumama
you never know what it is when you get it or lose it
sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
Tomorrow, huh...
Furious, Intense Chase
and Aggressive Dash
The Main Matches Begin
What's up? It's been a while.
Heh heh...
I was kind of in the hospital.
The hospital?
I'm totally fine, now.
Nothing to it!
I see.
— Ayame!
— Yes!
Here you go.
Pops?
Just eat it.
The final round is tomorrow, right?
Okay, then.
Thanks!
You've got a daughter at home,
so it's not so bad, right?
Most of my money vanishes
with the food expenses.
Moron. Your home is special, right?
Huh?
Girls are a drag.
Yeah. There are times when I really
don't get how to act with her.
Fathers have it rough...
Hah, am I the only bad guy?
Hey, mister.
Let me have everything
on these two pages, too!
Welcome!
Oh! Strong reinforcements!
Come on. You order something, too!
Hey... Dad.
Hmm?
Hey! Let's go home, already!
Excuse me?
Shut up. You're supposed to
live it up at a festival!
Festival, my ass...
What a drag.
You idiot... Since olden times...
the final round's
been like a festival!
I'm in that final round tomorrow.
Jeez, don't make me come to get you.
You're... in it?
Please, Dad...
Tomorrow, eh...
Yeah.
Tomorrow... is a full moon...
To think you didn't even
get a scratch...
Perfect, eh, Neji?
That's enough warm-up exercise...
Shall we get going?
I was nervous and couldn't sleep.
First... it's him...
in the first match.
Quite honestly... even my Sharingan
can't see through his Tenketsu!
The strongest man in the
Leaf is on my team.
It is that... Hyuga Neji!
Neji... Neji... Neji...
At last...
The first match is Hyuga Neji, right?!
Yeah. He's the number one rookie
from last year, right?!
We can't miss the first match!
Hyuga... Neji...
Now I can summon a frog...
It'll be okay.
They all... look nasty.
Hinata?
N-Naruto-kun.
W-What are you doing here?
Today is the final round, isn't it?
I... Just something...
I came to check out this training field.
This is the place where
I became Genin, so...
Really? W-Why?
N-Nothing... That doesn't matter!
Y-You're right. I'm sorry.
Say, Hinata...
Neji's a relative of yours, right?
Y-Yes.
Is he really strong...?
Yes...
I see.
B-But you might be able to win, Naruto-kun.
Yeah. I'm strong, after all!
I bet you can win, Naruto-kun.
What?
You know...
I... when you cheered for me,
I felt like I was able to become
stronger than before.
Hinata! Hang tough!
When the preliminaries ended,
I became able to like
myself just a little.
I'll...
stand...
by my own...
words.
That is my Ninja Way.
From someone else's standpoint,
it might not look like anything's changed...
but I feel like I was able to change.
I've been thinking that it was...
thanks to you, Naruto-kun.
Say, Hinata...
Did you really think so?
What?
I may look strong to you,
but all I do is mess up...
And I act tough because
I'm frustrated.
It's not like that!
Even when you messed up,
in my view... you were always
a proud failure.
W-When I look at you,
it impacts my heart.
You're not perfect, so...
So...
It's because you mess up...
that you have the strength
to rise up from that.
I think such strength is
true strength.
I... I think you're an
incredibly strong person.
Thanks, Hinata!
Even though I was always
the bottom one...
I was tense in the shoulders, somehow!
I was depressed,
which was totally not my character.
But I feel better now!
Naruto-kun...
Okay! I'm off to the match!
Hinata...
Huh?
I kind of... thought you were...
W-What...?
...gloomy, hesitant and weird.
Naruto-kun...
But I quite like... people...
like you!
...like you!
Oh, yeah! Be sure to come watch me
kick that Neji's butt!
Uh-oh. Time to run!
I-I'm late, late!
See you later, Hinata!
Sorry I'm late, Hinata.
Well, Shino's match isn't until
quite a bit later, so...
Hm? Hey? Hinata?
Hmm? W-What?
Oh, it's starting!
Move, move!
C'mon, move!
Damn it! There's quite a distance!
I won't make it!
Naruto nii-chan!
Konohamaru?!
I've come to aid in nii-chan's crisis, here!
Konohamaru...
What're you doing here?!
I'll tell you later!
This way, here!
There's an ace shortcut where
you can get straight to the arena, here!
What?!
All right!
Well done, Konohamaru!
Those who control the
secret path control time.
Oh, I see!
You're awesome, Konohamaru!
As I recall, there's a hole
in the wall around here...
Oh!
Here it is!
What's the matter, Konohamaru?
The secret path has been repaired, here!
What...?
Oh! There's no time!
Nii-chan!
Next approach!
Look! I'm really out of time.
It's a secret, but there's
an awesome path
that can get you inside the arena
in an instant, here!
What?! All right!
Well done, Konohamaru!
This hole is a shortcut?
It's a straight shot to
the final round arena!
No doubt, here!
Straight shot, huh?
Okay!
Let's hurry!
Yeah!
Konohamaru!
What's happening here?!
It's okay, here!
We're almost to the final
round arena, here!
See? There's the exit, here!
Oh, oh.
What?!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
T-This is... some kind of mistake!
Kooonooohaaamaaaruuu!
What the hell are you doing?!
We've gotten further
and further away!
Until just recently,
it was connected to the
final round arena, here.
Next approach, right away...
This is it!
If you ride this, you'll get to the
final round arena just like that, here!
Huh? A bull?
Think again, nii-chan.
A feudal lord Bull is not at all in
the same league as ordinary cows, here.
Once they start running,
even race horses grow deathly pale.
There's no way they can beat
a no-nonsense feudal lord cow!
Anyway, it's an awesome cow!
Nii-chan, if you leave the rest to this cow,
it's just a short run to
the final round arena, here!
Then, I'm counting on you.
Okay, let's go!
Huh? Wha...?!
Ouch!
What?
Nii-chan, go for it, here!
Hey! Stop! Stop!
Hey hey, we're missing quite
a few people.
What's going on?
It's going to start.
What's the meaning of this?
Sasuke-kun...?
And even Naruto...
Why is it?!
This is bad!
That's it!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Guys! Scatter the rampaging cows!
— Yeah!
What's wrong with you guys?
Why are you back, hey?!
More appeared!
The escape path was blocked!
It won't do any good to multiply!
Hmm? What the...?!
Uzumaki Naruto...?
We leave the rest to you!
Whoa, let us in, quick!
Hey!
Entry has already...!
What kind... of entrance is
this kid making...?
Naruto.
He's totally late.
What a drag.
Guys, run! A large herd of
stampeding bulls is coming.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Jeez! I'm serious.
So many of them...!
Huh? Hey...
Where's Sasuke?
The Dosu guy I'm supposed
to fight isn't here, either.
Hey, you guys there.
Don't be restless.
Throw out your chests and
show your faces to the spectators!
You guys are the stars of
this "final round".
ONE JAMPU ichiban SURAMU DANKU kamasu TAISON
One! first, Tyson jumps and slam-dunks
TWO are mo kore mo dosoku de HAGU KISSU I LOVE YOU
Two! he kisses and hugs everyone randomly and says "I love you"
THREE YOGA wo kiwamemasu KAREE kirai masara san
Three! Masala masters yoga but hates curry
FOUR hetare tougyuushi SANCHESU OREI
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter, olay!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
ONE kokuen bori ni bottou bodi ma haattaya san mo
One! Bodimahattaya devotes his time for digging black ships
TWO PEKIN DAKKU waiyaa AKUSHON chari de isogu CHEN RII
Two! peking Duck, action scene, Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
THREE MY KOTEKA daiji ni migakiageru POPO san
Three! Popo loves to polish his coteka
FOUR ote wo haishaku JAPANIIZU PIIPOO
Four! japanese people, now lend me your hand!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
sekaijuu hora kawatteku minna ganbatte so tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Hey, Hinata!
Keep your eyes open and watch me
defeat this unpleasant guy!
He goes and decides that
a person's life path can't be changed...
Destiny is decided when one is born?
Don't kid me!
People definitely can change.
By defeating this guy,
I'll prove that!
Next time:
"Byakugan vs Shadow Clones! I will definitely win!!"
Quit gabbing
and let's get started!